so psycho technology is anything
substance practice protocol on good
psychic technology is an internalized
tool into the psyche designed to alter
ideally improve cognition in some way
psycho technology is a tool that is
being integrated into the psyche that
allows one to then use that tool on the
psyche itself
I could technologies are invented and
then explained or taught and passed on
psycho technologies are learnt from
playing with a toy which then becomes a
tool which then becomes integrated into
the mind and in serves as a tool upon
the mind psycho technologies can be
anything at all they can be serious
practices they can be silly games
one of the fundamental secular
technologies is reading learning how to
unrig even more fundamental psycho
technology would be language for example
as one of our base psycho technologies
is language the psychic technology is a
feedback loop between the body and the
mind using the body to modulate the mind
and vice-versa
Eike technologies are also a feedback
loop between the mind body duality and
the external reality psycho technologies
allow for the manipulation the grouping
onto various aspects of one's psyche and
turning them like bolts I could
technologies they are the ability to
self examine one's own psyche what is
the psychic technological equivalent of
a hammer of a nail of a spanner of a
computer psychic technology is the use
of a tool as a metaphor which then
becomes real becomes real inside of
one's mind allows to metaphorically
transform one's mind cycle technologies
are temporary tools psycho technologies
are tools that we can conjure inside of
our
mind to reorganize the structure of our
own mind to rebuild our mind to return
to recoat our mind who what extent our
psycho technologies voluntary and
involuntary to what extent we simply
absorbed them involuntarily born into an
ecosystem of psycho technologies but
then becoming aware of on psycho
technologies incoming sovereign over
them born into an ecosystem psycho set
knowledge that's very good
and so those psycho technologies become
accepted wisdom almost akin to reality
itself mmm psycho technologies that we
use shape our psyche and shapes shut
psyches let in specific dimensions so
psycho technologies are inextricably
linked from our experience of reality
and the ability to tweet them is thus to
enter into other realities psycho
technologies are the tools to shape the
temple of our psyche either technologies
give us broader access to the infinite
potentials of perception and awareness
psycho technologies are the tools that
we use to tend to the potential of
within the body is is is inextricably
linked from our being and so psycho
technologies must also include things
which prime the body fundamental psycho
technology is a breath yes that's the
beginning that's the that's the first of
all of them from the first psycho
technology of the breath is born the
second psycho technology the dance
responding to the so so what extent is
sensual perception of psycho technology
because it's not reality is it
modulating one sensory perception is
like a technological and modulating one
sensory perception is something that we
learn from the moment we emerge from the
womb possibly even before that and so we
engage cycle Wingert cycle technology is
the use of the psyche as a tool to
employ the term cycle technology implies
a certain conscious awareness of that
tool though and so yeah one can go very
deep psychic technology is tool
awareness applied chemical psyche
awareness so knowing that I'm holding
the hammer rather than just wielding the
hammer sort of thing as as crude analogy
with something like that psycho
technology is recognizing that one can
use one psyche to transform the psyche
of oneself in the world using one psyche
to to transform not reality but one's
experience of reality which is
tantamount to exactly the same thing
right
we use our psychic technologies to carve
our reality tunnels
our psycho technologies are the
architecture with which we make order
and meaning out of the world for
ourselves with our psycho technologies
we can draw blueprints of our psyche
psycho technologies are in a constant
state of development as they feed back
into the psyche and develop that psycho
technology is the psyche as a self
improving tool I could technologies are
embedded deep within our not DNA but
deep within our being psycho technology
is the use of a tool within our cells
and deep inside our psyche is there a
psycho technology with which to evaluate
the effectiveness of psycho technology's
psycho technologies of measurement
psycho technologies of circumscription
psycho technologies of building even
that psycho technologies are informing
and developing our psyches our ability
to measure the effectiveness of the
psyche of Technology is rooted in the
psyche which is using psycho
technologies to measure the shape of the
psyche and the effectiveness of the
tools within so what extensions psycho
technologies be treated as objective
phenomena given that they exist within
the subjective realm of the individual
psyche psycho technologies as in this
objectively tested technologies to shape
consciousness in specific ways into
subjectively tested as opposed to object
yes so if there is agreement as to their
effectiveness then that yes a research
project to study
the objective correlates of specific
psycho technologies designing metrics
that can effectively convey the
effectiveness of a given psycho
technology
designing quantitative and qualitative
metrics for the measurement of the
effectiveness of psycho technology's
metrics which do not transmute the value
of the slice like a technology into
something mundane and profane the sacred
quality of psycho technologies and the
ethics of psycho technologies